{
    "QuizID": "A2",
    "QuizContent": [
        {
            "QuestionID": "1",
            "Question": "What was the name of the first transaction code for the ABAP Workbench?",
            "Content": [],
            "Answers": {
                "A": "SE80",
                "B": "SWB",
                "C": "SE38",
                "D": "SEU"
            },
            "RightAnswer": "D",
            "Explanation": ""
        },
        {
            "QuestionID": "2",
            "Question": "How many times did ADT win at the TechEd Demo Jam?",
            "Content": [],
            "Answers": {
                "A": "1",
                "B": "2",
                "C": "3",
                "D": "Not once"
            },
            "RightAnswer": "B",
            "Explanation": ""
        },
        {
            "QuestionID": "3",
            "Question": "How do you work with ADT in parallel in multiple systems?",
            "Content": [],
            "Answers": {
                "A": "Create an ADT project per system, context menu \"Open in Project\"",
                "B": "Menu entry \"Open remote object\" in the ABAP Editor",
                "C": "Menu entry \"Compare objects\" in Project Explorer",
                "D": "No support"
            },
            "RightAnswer": "A",
            "Explanation": ""
        },
        {
            "QuestionID": "4",
            "Question": "How to insert code patterns in ADT?",
            "Content": [],
            "Answers": {
                "A": "Double click on an entry in the Patterns view",
                "B": "Double click on an entry in the Templates view",
                "C": "By double-clicking an entry in the ABAP Templates Preferences",
                "D": "Calling the function \"Insert signature\""
            },
            "RightAnswer": "B",
            "Explanation": ""
        },
        {
            "QuestionID": "5",
            "Question": "From which release can ADT be used?",
            "Content": [],
            "Answers": {
                "A": "7.02",
                "B": "7.20",
                "C": "7.31",
                "D": "7.40"
            },
            "RightAnswer": "C",
            "Explanation": "ADT can be used on the system as of version 7.31, but the scope of views and functions always depends on the backend release."
        },
        {
            "QuestionID": "6",
            "Question": "Which editor functionality allows to automatically correct errors?",
            "Content": [],
            "Answers": {
                "A": "Quick Fixes",
                "B": "Quick Assists",
                "C": "Quick Solutions",
                "D": "Quick Access"
            },
            "RightAnswer": "B",
            "Explanation": ""
        },
        {
            "QuestionID": "7",
            "Question": "With which Eclipse release was ADT initially released",
            "Content": [],
            "Answers": {
                "A": "Indigo",
                "B": "Kepler",
                "C": "Ganymede",
                "D": "Dark Moon"
            },
            "RightAnswer": "A",
            "Explanation": ""
        },
        {
            "QuestionID": "8",
            "Question": "On which operating system is ADT not officially supported?",
            "Content": [],
            "Answers": {
                "A": "Windows",
                "B": "Mac",
                "C": "Linux"
            },
            "RightAnswer": "C",
            "Explanation": ""
        },
        {
            "QuestionID": "9",
            "Question": "Which shortcut can be used to highlight and evaluate ABAP unit code coverage results?",
            "Content": [],
            "Answers": {
                "A": "Alt Shift F11",
                "B": "Ctrl Shift F11",
                "C": "Ctrl Shift F12",
                "D": "Alt Shift F12"
            },
            "RightAnswer": "B",
            "Explanation": ""
        },
        {
            "QuestionID": "10",
            "Question": "What is not supported in the ABAP Development Tools (ADT) with an Eclipse-based editor?",
            "Content": [],
            "Answers": {
                "A": "ABAP Classes",
                "B": "Web Dynpro",
                "C": "Dynpros",
                "D": "Tables"
            },
            "RightAnswer": "C",
            "Explanation": ""
        }
    ]
}